<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cvrf:cvrfdoc xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:cvrf-common="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/common" xmlns:cvrf="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/cvrf">
  <cvrf:DocumentTitle>Vulnerabilities in OpenSSL Affecting Cisco Products: November 2022</cvrf:DocumentTitle>
  <cvrf:DocumentType>Cisco Security Advisory</cvrf:DocumentType>
  <cvrf:DocumentPublisher Type="Vendor">
    <cvrf:ContactDetails>Emergency Support:
+1 877 228 7302 (toll-free within North America)
+1 408 525 6532 (International direct-dial)
Non-emergency Support:
Email: psirt@cisco.com
Support requests that are received via e-mail are typically acknowledged within 48 hours.</cvrf:ContactDetails>
    <cvrf:IssuingAuthority>Cisco product security incident response is the responsibility of the Cisco Product Security Incident Response Team (PSIRT). The Cisco PSIRT is a dedicated, global team that manages the receipt, investigation, and public reporting of security vulnerability information that is related to Cisco products and networks. The on-call Cisco PSIRT works 24x7 with Cisco customers, independent security researchers, consultants, industry organizations, and other vendors to identify possible security issues with Cisco products and networks.
More information can be found in Cisco Security Vulnerability Policy available at http://www.cisco.com/web/about/security/psirt/security_vulnerability_policy.html</cvrf:IssuingAuthority>
  </cvrf:DocumentPublisher>
  <cvrf:DocumentTracking>
    <cvrf:Identification>
      <cvrf:ID>cisco-sa-openssl-W9sdCc2a</cvrf:ID>
    </cvrf:Identification>
    <cvrf:Status>Final</cvrf:Status>
    <cvrf:Version>1.5</cvrf:Version>
    <cvrf:RevisionHistory>
      <cvrf:Revision>
        <cvrf:Number>1.0</cvrf:Number>
        <cvrf:Date>2022-10-28T21:40:41</cvrf:Date>
        <cvrf:Description>Initial public release.</cvrf:Description>
      </cvrf:Revision>
      <cvrf:Revision>
        <cvrf:Number>1.1</cvrf:Number>
        <cvrf:Date>2022-11-01T20:23:02</cvrf:Date>
        <cvrf:Description>Update with OpenSSL public announcement.</cvrf:Description>
      </cvrf:Revision>
      <cvrf:Revision>
        <cvrf:Number>1.2</cvrf:Number>
        <cvrf:Date>2022-11-02T19:26:36</cvrf:Date>
        <cvrf:Description>Update products under investigation and products confirmed not vulnerable.</cvrf:Description>
      </cvrf:Revision>
      <cvrf:Revision>
        <cvrf:Number>1.3</cvrf:Number>
        <cvrf:Date>2022-11-03T20:12:42</cvrf:Date>
        <cvrf:Description>Update products under investigation, vulnerable products, and products confirmed not vulnerable.</cvrf:Description>
      </cvrf:Revision>
      <cvrf:Revision>
        <cvrf:Number>1.4</cvrf:Number>
        <cvrf:Date>2022-11-04T18:40:16</cvrf:Date>
        <cvrf:Description>Update affected products and disposition of cloud offers.</cvrf:Description>
      </cvrf:Revision>
      <cvrf:Revision>
        <cvrf:Number>1.5</cvrf:Number>
        <cvrf:Date>2022-11-08T20:57:38</cvrf:Date>
        <cvrf:Description>Update summary, affected products, and disposition of cloud offers.</cvrf:Description>
      </cvrf:Revision>
    </cvrf:RevisionHistory>
    <cvrf:InitialReleaseDate>2022-10-28T16:00:00</cvrf:InitialReleaseDate>
    <cvrf:CurrentReleaseDate>2022-11-08T20:57:38</cvrf:CurrentReleaseDate>
    <cvrf:Generator>
      <cvrf:Engine>TVCE</cvrf:Engine>
    </cvrf:Generator>
  </cvrf:DocumentTracking>
  <cvrf:DocumentNotes>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Summary" Type="Summary" Ordinal="1">On November 1, 2022, the OpenSSL Project announced the following vulnerabilities:

CVE-2022-3602 - X.509 Email Address 4-byte Buffer Overflow
CVE-2022-3786 - X.509 Email Address Variable Length Buffer Overflow

For a description of these vulnerabilities, see OpenSSL Security Advisory [Nov 1 2022] ["https://www.openssl.org/news/secadv/20221101.txt"].

This advisory is available at the following link:
https://tools.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-openssl-W9sdCc2a ["https://tools.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-openssl-W9sdCc2a"]</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Affected Products" Type="General" Ordinal="2">Cisco investigated its product line to determine which products and cloud services may be affected by these vulnerabilities. OpenSSL 3.x is not widely used in Cisco products and cloud offers, and only products that may contain the affected software are listed in this advisory. If a product or cloud offer is not explicitly listed in this advisory, it is not vulnerable.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Vulnerable Products" Type="General" Ordinal="3">The following table lists Cisco products that are affected by one or more of the vulnerabilities that are described in this advisory. If a future release date is indicated for software, the date provided represents an estimate based on all information known to Cisco as of the Last Updated date at the top of the advisory. Availability dates are subject to change based on a number of factors, including satisfactory testing results and delivery of other priority features and fixes. If no version or date is listed for an affected component (indicated by a blank field and/or an advisory designation of Interim), Cisco is continuing to evaluate the fix and will update the advisory as additional information becomes available. After the advisory is marked Final, customers should refer to the associated Cisco bug(s) for further details.
        Product  Cisco Bug ID  Fixed Release Availability ["https://tools.cisco.com/security/center/resources/security_vulnerability_policy.html#fixes"]      Network Management and Provisioning      IoT Field Network Director, formerly Connected Grid Network Management System  CSCwd44112 ["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCwd44112"]  4.8.1 (Available)
4.9.0 (Available)
5.0.0 (May 2023)</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Products Confirmed Not Vulnerable" Type="General" Ordinal="4">Only products that may contain the affected software are listed in this advisory. If a product or cloud offer is not explicitly listed in this advisory, it is not vulnerable.

Cisco has confirmed that this vulnerability does not affect the following Cisco products:

Cable Devices

Ultra Cloud Core - Network Repository Function
Ultra Cloud Core - User Plane Function

Network and Content Security Devices

Identity Services Engine (ISE)
Secure Network Analytics

Network Management and Provisioning

Application Policy Infrastructure Controller (APIC)
Container Platform
Data Center Network Manager (DCNM)
Elastic Services Controller (ESC)
Evolved Programmable Network Manager
Nexus Dashboard, formerly known as Application Services Engine
Prime Infrastructure

Routing and Switching - Enterprise and Service Provider

SD-WAN vAnalytics Software
SD-WAN vManage Software
Ultra Cloud Core - Policy Control Function
Ultra Cloud Core - Redundancy Configuration Manager
Ultra Cloud Core - Subscriber Microservices Infrastructure

Unified Computing

HyperFlex System
UCS Blade Server - Integrated Management Controller
UCS Manager

   Cisco Cloud Offerings

Cisco investigated its cloud offers to determine which products may be affected by these vulnerabilities. The following table lists Cisco cloud offers that are under investigation. Only cloud offers known to possibly be affected are listed. If a cloud offer is not explicitly listed in this advisory, it is not vulnerable.

        Product  Disposition      AppDynamics  Not affected      CX Cloud  Not affected      Duo  Not affected      Intersight  Not affected      Meraki  Not affected      SD-WAN  Not affected      SecureX  Not affected      ThousandEyes  Not affected      Umbrella  Not affected      Unified Communications Manager Cloud  Not affected      Webex Calling  Not affected      Webex Cloud-Connected UC  Not affected      Webex Contact Center  Not affected      Webex Teams  Not affected</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Workarounds" Type="General" Ordinal="5">Any workarounds for a specific Cisco product or service will be documented in the relevant Cisco bugs, which are identified in the Vulnerable Products ["#vp"] section of this advisory.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Fixed Software" Type="General" Ordinal="6">For information about fixed software releases ["https://tools.cisco.com/security/center/resources/security_vulnerability_policy.html#fixes"], consult the Cisco bugs identified in the Vulnerable Products ["#vp"] section of this advisory.

When considering software upgrades ["https://tools.cisco.com/security/center/resources/security_vulnerability_policy.html#fixes"], customers are advised to regularly consult the advisories for Cisco products, which are available from the Cisco Security Advisories ["https://www.cisco.com/go/psirt"] page, to determine exposure and a complete upgrade solution.

In all cases, customers should ensure that the devices to be upgraded contain sufficient memory and confirm that current hardware and software configurations will continue to be supported properly by the new release. If the information is not clear, customers are advised to contact the Cisco Technical Assistance Center (TAC) or their contracted maintenance providers.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Vulnerability Policy" Type="General" Ordinal="7">To learn about Cisco security vulnerability disclosure policies and publications, see the Security Vulnerability Policy ["http://www.cisco.com/web/about/security/psirt/security_vulnerability_policy.html"]. This document also contains instructions for obtaining fixed software and receiving security vulnerability information from Cisco.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Exploitation and Public Announcements" Type="General" Ordinal="8">The Cisco Product Security Incident Response Team (PSIRT) is not aware of any malicious use of the vulnerabilities that are described in this advisory.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Source" Type="General" Ordinal="9">These vulnerabilities were publicly disclosed by the OpenSSL Software Foundation on November 1, 2022.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Legal Disclaimer" Type="Legal Disclaimer" Ordinal="10">THIS DOCUMENT IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS AND DOES NOT IMPLY ANY KIND OF GUARANTEE OR WARRANTY, INCLUDING THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR USE. YOUR USE OF THE INFORMATION ON THE DOCUMENT OR MATERIALS LINKED FROM THE DOCUMENT IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. CISCO RESERVES THE RIGHT TO CHANGE OR UPDATE THIS DOCUMENT AT ANY TIME.

A standalone copy or paraphrase of the text of this document that omits the distribution URL is an uncontrolled copy and may lack important information or contain factual errors. The information in this document is intended for end users of Cisco products.</cvrf:Note>
  </cvrf:DocumentNotes>
  <cvrf:DocumentReferences>
    <cvrf:Reference Type="Self">
      <cvrf:URL>https://tools.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-openssl-W9sdCc2a</cvrf:URL>
      <cvrf:Description>Vulnerabilities in OpenSSL Affecting Cisco Products: November 2022</cvrf:Description>
    </cvrf:Reference>
  </cvrf:DocumentReferences>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="1" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>X.509 Email Address 4-byte Buffer Overflow, Other Vulnerability</Title>
    <CVE>CVE-2022-3602</CVE>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>Any workarounds for a specific Cisco product or service will be documented in the relevant Cisco bugs, which are identified in the Vulnerable Products ["#vp"] section of this advisory.</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://tools.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-openssl-W9sdCc2a</URL>
        <Description>Vulnerabilities in OpenSSL Affecting Cisco Products: November 2022</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="2" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>X.509 Email Address Variable Length Buffer Overflow, Other Vulnerability</Title>
    <CVE>CVE-2022-3786</CVE>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>Any workarounds for a specific Cisco product or service will be documented in the relevant Cisco bugs, which are identified in the Vulnerable Products ["#vp"] section of this advisory.</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://tools.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-openssl-W9sdCc2a</URL>
        <Description>Vulnerabilities in OpenSSL Affecting Cisco Products: November 2022</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
</cvrf:cvrfdoc>