<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cvrf:cvrfdoc xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:cvrf-common="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/common" xmlns:cvrf="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/cvrf">
  <cvrf:DocumentTitle>Cisco Identity Services Engine Vulnerabilities</cvrf:DocumentTitle>
  <cvrf:DocumentType>Cisco Security Advisory</cvrf:DocumentType>
  <cvrf:DocumentPublisher Type="Vendor">
    <cvrf:ContactDetails>Emergency Support:
+1 877 228 7302 (toll-free within North America)
+1 408 525 6532 (International direct-dial)
Non-emergency Support:
Email: psirt@cisco.com
Support requests that are received via e-mail are typically acknowledged within 48 hours.</cvrf:ContactDetails>
    <cvrf:IssuingAuthority>Cisco product security incident response is the responsibility of the Cisco Product Security Incident Response Team (PSIRT). The Cisco PSIRT is a dedicated, global team that manages the receipt, investigation, and public reporting of security vulnerability information that is related to Cisco products and networks. The on-call Cisco PSIRT works 24x7 with Cisco customers, independent security researchers, consultants, industry organizations, and other vendors to identify possible security issues with Cisco products and networks.
More information can be found in Cisco Security Vulnerability Policy available at http://www.cisco.com/web/about/security/psirt/security_vulnerability_policy.html</cvrf:IssuingAuthority>
  </cvrf:DocumentPublisher>
  <cvrf:DocumentTracking>
    <cvrf:Identification>
      <cvrf:ID>cisco-sa-ise-7Q4TNYUx</cvrf:ID>
    </cvrf:Identification>
    <cvrf:Status>Interim</cvrf:Status>
    <cvrf:Version>1.1</cvrf:Version>
    <cvrf:RevisionHistory>
      <cvrf:Revision>
        <cvrf:Number>1.0</cvrf:Number>
        <cvrf:Date>2022-11-16T16:02:19</cvrf:Date>
        <cvrf:Description>Initial public release.</cvrf:Description>
      </cvrf:Revision>
      <cvrf:Revision>
        <cvrf:Number>1.1</cvrf:Number>
        <cvrf:Date>2022-11-16T20:35:41</cvrf:Date>
        <cvrf:Description>Updated footnotes in the fixed release table and updated name of the researcher.</cvrf:Description>
      </cvrf:Revision>
    </cvrf:RevisionHistory>
    <cvrf:InitialReleaseDate>2022-11-16T16:00:00</cvrf:InitialReleaseDate>
    <cvrf:CurrentReleaseDate>2022-11-16T20:35:41</cvrf:CurrentReleaseDate>
    <cvrf:Generator>
      <cvrf:Engine>TVCE</cvrf:Engine>
    </cvrf:Generator>
  </cvrf:DocumentTracking>
  <cvrf:DocumentNotes>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Summary" Type="Summary" Ordinal="1">Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to inject arbitrary operating system commands, bypass security protections, and conduct cross-site scripting attacks.

For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details ["#details"] section of this advisory.

Cisco plans to release software updates that address these vulnerabilities. There are no workarounds that address these vulnerabilities.

This advisory is available at the following link:
https://tools.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-ise-7Q4TNYUx ["https://tools.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-ise-7Q4TNYUx"]</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Vulnerable Products" Type="General" Ordinal="2">These vulnerabilities affect Cisco ISE.

For information about which Cisco software releases are vulnerable, see the Fixed Software ["#fs"] section of this advisory.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Products Confirmed Not Vulnerable" Type="General" Ordinal="3">Only products listed in the Vulnerable Products ["#vp"] section of this advisory are known to be affected by these vulnerabilities.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Details" Type="General" Ordinal="4">The vulnerabilities are not dependent on one another. Exploitation of one of the vulnerabilities is not required to exploit another vulnerability. In addition, a software release that is affected by one of the vulnerabilities may not be affected by the other vulnerabilities.

Note: These vulnerabilities can be exploited only by valid and authorized users of the Cisco ISE system. As a best practice, customers can restrict console access and admin web access. To configure the access restrictions, choose Administration &gt; System &gt; Admin Access &gt; Settings &gt; Access &gt; IP Access.

Details about the vulnerabilities are as follows:

CVE-2022-20964: Cisco Identity Services Engine tcpdump Feature Command Injection Vulnerability

A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to inject arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system.

This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user input within requests as part of the web-based management interface tcpdump feature. An attacker with privileges sufficient to access the tcpdump feature could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating requests to the web-based management interface to contain operating system commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary operating system commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of the web services user. The chaining of further issues could allow an attacker with command line access to elevate privileges to root and gain complete control over the system.

Cisco plans to release software updates that address this vulnerability. There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.

Bug ID(s): CSCwc98823 ["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCwc98823"]
CVE ID: CVE-2022-20964
Security Impact Rating (SIR): High
CVSS Base Score: 6.3
CVSS Vector: CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L

CVE-2022-20966: Cisco Identity Services Engine tcpdump Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability

A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct cross-site scripting attacks against other users of the application web-based management interface.

This vulnerability is due to improper validation of input to an application feature before storage within the web-based management interface tcpdump feature. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by creating entries that contain malicious HTML or script code within the application interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious HTML or script code within the application interface for use in further cross-site scripting attacks.

Cisco plans to release software updates that address this vulnerability. There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.

Bug ID(s): CSCwc98831 ["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCwc98831"]
CVE ID: CVE-2022-20966
Security Impact Rating (SIR): Medium
CVSS Base Score: 5.4
CVSS Vector: CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N

CVE-2022-20967: Cisco Identity Services Engine External RADIUS Server Feature Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability

A vulnerability in the web-based management interface External RADIUS Server feature of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct cross-site scripting attacks against other users of the application web-based management interface.

This vulnerability is due to improper validation of input to an application feature before storage within the External RADIUS Server feature of the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by creating entries within the application interface that contain malicious HTML or script code. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious HTML or script code within the application interface for use in further cross-site scripting attacks.

Cisco plans to release software updates that address this vulnerability. There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.

Bug ID(s): CSCwc98833 ["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCwc98833"]
CVE ID: CVE-2022-20967
Security Impact Rating (SIR): Medium
CVSS Base Score: 4.8
CVSS Vector: CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N

CVE-2022-20965: Cisco Identity Services Engine Access Bypass Vulnerability

A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to bypass security restrictions within the web-based management interface.

This vulnerability is due to improper access control on a feature within the web-based management interface of the affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing features through direct requests, thus bypassing checks within the application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to take privileged actions within the web-based management interface that should be otherwise restricted.

Cisco plans to release software updates that address this vulnerability. There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.

Bug ID(s): CSCwc98828 ["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCwc98833"]
CVE ID: CVE-2022-20965
Security Impact Rating (SIR): Medium
CVSS Base Score: 4.3
CVSS Vector: CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Workarounds" Type="General" Ordinal="5">There are no workarounds that address these vulnerabilities.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Fixed Software" Type="General" Ordinal="6">Cisco plans to release free software updates ["https://tools.cisco.com/security/center/resources/security_vulnerability_policy.html#ssu"] that address the vulnerabilities described in this advisory. Customers with service contracts that entitle them to regular software updates should obtain security fixes through their usual update channels.

Customers may only install and expect support for software versions and feature sets for which they have purchased a license. By installing, downloading, accessing, or otherwise using such software upgrades, customers agree to follow the terms of the Cisco software license:
https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/products/end-user-license-agreement.html ["https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/products/end-user-license-agreement.html"]

Additionally, customers may only download software for which they have a valid license, procured from Cisco directly, or through a Cisco authorized reseller or partner. In most cases this will be a maintenance upgrade to software that was previously purchased. Free security software updates do not entitle customers to a new software license, additional software feature sets, or major revision upgrades.

The Cisco Support and Downloads page ["https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/support/index.html"] on Cisco.com provides information about licensing and downloads. This page can also display customer device support coverage for customers who use the My Devices tool.

When considering software upgrades ["https://tools.cisco.com/security/center/resources/security_vulnerability_policy.html#fixes"], customers are advised to regularly consult the advisories for Cisco products, which are available from the Cisco Security Advisories page ["https://www.cisco.com/go/psirt"], to determine exposure and a complete upgrade solution.

In all cases, customers should ensure that the devices to be upgraded contain sufficient memory and confirm that current hardware and software configurations will continue to be supported properly by the new release. If the information is not clear, customers are advised to contact the Cisco Technical Assistance Center (TAC) or their contracted maintenance providers.
  Customers Without Service Contracts
Customers who purchase directly from Cisco but do not hold a Cisco service contract and customers who make purchases through third-party vendors but are unsuccessful in obtaining fixed software through their point of sale should obtain upgrades by contacting the Cisco TAC: https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/support/web/tsd-cisco-worldwide-contacts.html ["https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/support/web/tsd-cisco-worldwide-contacts.html"]

Customers should have the product serial number available and be prepared to provide the URL of this advisory as evidence of entitlement to a free upgrade.
      Fixed Releases
In the following table(s), the left column lists Cisco software releases. The right column indicates whether a release is affected by the vulnerabilities that are described in this advisory and the first release that includes the fix for these vulnerabilities. Customers are advised to upgrade to an appropriate fixed software release ["https://tools.cisco.com/security/center/resources/security_vulnerability_policy.html#fixes"] as indicated in this section.
        Cisco ISE Release  First Fixed Release          2.72 and earlier  Migrate to a fixed release.      3.02 and earlier  Migrate to a fixed release.      3.11  3.1p6 (Mar 2023)      3.21  3.2p1 (Jan 2023)
1. Hot patches could be available by request for the following Cisco ISE releases and patch levels: 3.1p5 and 3.2. Contact Cisco TAC to make the request.
2. Cisco is evaluating fixes for Cisco ISE releases 2.7 and 3.0.
For instructions on upgrading a device, see the Upgrade Guides located on the Cisco Identity Service Engine ["https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/support/security/identity-services-engine/series.html"] support page.

The Cisco Product Security Incident Response Team (PSIRT) validates only the affected and fixed release information that is documented in this advisory.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Vulnerability Policy" Type="General" Ordinal="7">To learn about Cisco security vulnerability disclosure policies and publications, see the Security Vulnerability Policy ["http://www.cisco.com/web/about/security/psirt/security_vulnerability_policy.html"]. This document also contains instructions for obtaining fixed software and receiving security vulnerability information from Cisco.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Exploitation and Public Announcements" Type="General" Ordinal="8">The Cisco PSIRT is aware that proof-of-concept exploit code for the vulnerabilities that are described in this advisory will become available after software fixes are released. Public reports of the vulnerabilities, including a description and classification without specific technical details, may become available after this advisory is published.

The Cisco PSIRT is not aware of any malicious use of the vulnerabilities that are described in this advisory.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Source" Type="General" Ordinal="9">Cisco would like to thank Davide Virruso of Yoroi for reporting these vulnerabilities.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Legal Disclaimer" Type="Legal Disclaimer" Ordinal="10">THIS DOCUMENT IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS AND DOES NOT IMPLY ANY KIND OF GUARANTEE OR WARRANTY, INCLUDING THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR USE. YOUR USE OF THE INFORMATION ON THE DOCUMENT OR MATERIALS LINKED FROM THE DOCUMENT IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. CISCO RESERVES THE RIGHT TO CHANGE OR UPDATE THIS DOCUMENT AT ANY TIME. CISCO EXPECTS TO UPDATE THIS DOCUMENT AS NEW INFORMATION BECOMES AVAILABLE.

A standalone copy or paraphrase of the text of this document that omits the distribution URL is an uncontrolled copy and may lack important information or contain factual errors. The information in this document is intended for end users of Cisco products.</cvrf:Note>
  </cvrf:DocumentNotes>
  <cvrf:DocumentReferences>
    <cvrf:Reference Type="Self">
      <cvrf:URL>https://tools.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-ise-7Q4TNYUx</cvrf:URL>
      <cvrf:Description>Cisco Identity Services Engine Vulnerabilities</cvrf:Description>
    </cvrf:Reference>
  </cvrf:DocumentReferences>
  <ProductTree xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/prod">
    <Branch Name="Cisco" Type="Vendor">
      <Branch Name="Cisco Identity Services Engine Software" Type="Product Name">
        <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-111903">Cisco Identity Services Engine Software </FullProductName>
      </Branch>
    </Branch>
  </ProductTree>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="1" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>vuln-CVE-2022-20964</Title>
    <ID SystemName="Cisco Bug ID">CSCwc98823</ID>
    <Notes>
      <Note Title="Cisco Bug IDs" Type="Other" Ordinal="1">CSCwc98823</Note>
      <Note Title="Affected Product Comprehensiveness" Type="Other" Ordinal="2">Complete.</Note>
    </Notes>
    <CVE>CVE-2022-20964</CVE>
    <ProductStatuses>
      <Status Type="Known Affected">
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-111903</ProductID>
      </Status>
    </ProductStatuses>
    <CVSSScoreSets>
      <ScoreSetV3>
        <BaseScoreV3>6.3</BaseScoreV3>
        <VectorV3>CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L</VectorV3>
      </ScoreSetV3>
    </CVSSScoreSets>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>There are no workarounds that address these vulnerabilities.</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://tools.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-ise-7Q4TNYUx</URL>
        <Description>Cisco Identity Services Engine Vulnerabilities</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="2" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>vuln-CVE-2022-20965</Title>
    <ID SystemName="Cisco Bug ID">CSCwc98828</ID>
    <Notes>
      <Note Title="Cisco Bug IDs" Type="Other" Ordinal="1">CSCwc98828</Note>
      <Note Title="Affected Product Comprehensiveness" Type="Other" Ordinal="2">Complete.</Note>
    </Notes>
    <CVE>CVE-2022-20965</CVE>
    <ProductStatuses>
      <Status Type="Known Affected">
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-111903</ProductID>
      </Status>
    </ProductStatuses>
    <CVSSScoreSets>
      <ScoreSetV3>
        <BaseScoreV3>4.3</BaseScoreV3>
        <VectorV3>CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N</VectorV3>
      </ScoreSetV3>
    </CVSSScoreSets>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>There are no workarounds that address these vulnerabilities.</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://tools.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-ise-7Q4TNYUx</URL>
        <Description>Cisco Identity Services Engine Vulnerabilities</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="3" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>vuln-CVE-2022-20966</Title>
    <ID SystemName="Cisco Bug ID">CSCwc98831</ID>
    <Notes>
      <Note Title="Cisco Bug IDs" Type="Other" Ordinal="1">CSCwc98831</Note>
      <Note Title="Affected Product Comprehensiveness" Type="Other" Ordinal="2">Complete.</Note>
    </Notes>
    <CVE>CVE-2022-20966</CVE>
    <ProductStatuses>
      <Status Type="Known Affected">
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-111903</ProductID>
      </Status>
    </ProductStatuses>
    <CVSSScoreSets>
      <ScoreSetV3>
        <BaseScoreV3>5.4</BaseScoreV3>
        <VectorV3>CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N</VectorV3>
      </ScoreSetV3>
    </CVSSScoreSets>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>There are no workarounds that address these vulnerabilities.</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://tools.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-ise-7Q4TNYUx</URL>
        <Description>Cisco Identity Services Engine Vulnerabilities</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="4" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>vuln-CVE-2022-20967</Title>
    <ID SystemName="Cisco Bug ID">CSCwc98833</ID>
    <Notes>
      <Note Title="Cisco Bug IDs" Type="Other" Ordinal="1">CSCwc98833</Note>
      <Note Title="Affected Product Comprehensiveness" Type="Other" Ordinal="2">Complete.</Note>
    </Notes>
    <CVE>CVE-2022-20967</CVE>
    <ProductStatuses>
      <Status Type="Known Affected">
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-111903</ProductID>
      </Status>
    </ProductStatuses>
    <CVSSScoreSets>
      <ScoreSetV3>
        <BaseScoreV3>4.8</BaseScoreV3>
        <VectorV3>CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N</VectorV3>
      </ScoreSetV3>
    </CVSSScoreSets>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>There are no workarounds that address these vulnerabilities.</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://tools.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-ise-7Q4TNYUx</URL>
        <Description>Cisco Identity Services Engine Vulnerabilities</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
</cvrf:cvrfdoc>